[upbeat music]
[DJ over phone] Next question: Besides the U.S.,
下一个问题：除了美国，
where else does superstar Candace Parker play professional basketball?
超级巨星坎迪斯·帕克还在哪里打职业篮球？
- Russia. - Correct.
- 俄罗斯。 - 正确。
You're two questions away from winning the grand prize:
你再答对两个问题就能赢得大奖：
lunch with Candace Parker.
与坎迪斯·帕克共进午餐。
I'm ready. Hit me.
我准备好了。来吧。
- How many brothers does Candace have?
- 坎迪斯有几个兄弟？
Three: Anthony, Marcus, and LT.
三个：安东尼、马库斯和LT。
Ba-boom!
棒极了！
[DJ] Whoa, you really are a fan.
哇，你真的是个粉丝啊。
Super-fan.
超级粉丝。
Plus we have a lot in common.
而且我们有很多共同点。
I also have brothers, and I'm pretty sure
我也有兄弟，而且我敢肯定
Candace knows how annoying they can be--
Candace知道他们有多烦人——
always butting in my business.
总是插手我的事情。
Hear that?
听到了吗？
She said we're always butting in her business.
她说我们总是插手她的事情。
How dare she?
她怎么敢这么说？
[DJ] Okay, Dawn, last question.
好吧，Dawn，最后一个问题。
What is Candace's favorite root vegetable?
Candace最喜欢的根茎类蔬菜是什么？
Yes!
是的！
The answer is her--
答案是她的--
[static over phone]
[电话中的静电声]
[DJ] I'm sorry, you're breaking up.
对不起，你的信号不好。
Dicky!
Dicky！
Wait, are you guys on the phone?
等等，你们在打电话吗？
Do you think she can hear us?
你觉得她能听到我们吗？
[Dawn over phone] Hang up!
挂断！
All right. I got this one.
好的。我知道这个。
The answer is--
答案是--
[dial tone, all gasp]
[拨号音，所有人惊呼]
[all whispering] Ah!
[所有人低声说] 啊！
Hello?
喂？
Hello? Yam. The answer's yam!
喂？Yam。答案是红薯！
[phone thuds]
[电话砰的一声]
[rumbling footsteps]
[沉重的脚步声]
What have we done?
我们做了什么？
[rumbling footsteps]
[沉重的脚步声]
How mad do you think she'll be?
你觉得她会有多生气？
[rumbling footsteps] - That mad.
非常生气。
[rumbling footsteps]
（脚步声）
She's gonna scream at us like she's never screamed before.
她会像以前从未有过的那样对我们大吼大叫。
So far so good.
到目前为止还不错。
It's worse than I thought.
比我想象的还要糟糕。
She's so mad, she didn't scream at all.
她气到连骂都不骂了。
That's her worst kind of mad.
那是她最糟糕的生气方式。
Hey, looking good there, kiddo.
嘿，看起来不错啊，孩子。
Love that blouse.
喜欢那件衬衫。
Ah, making a healthy smoothie, huh?
啊，在做健康的 smoothie 呢，是吧？
Good choices.
好选择。
Ow. That's a lot of carrot.
哎哟。这么多胡萝卜。
Look, we feel really bad we messed up the contest for you.
看，我们真的很抱歉因为我们的失误影响了你的比赛。
So we'd like to say something from the heart
所以我们想发自内心地说一些
that we don't say very often.
我们不常说的话。
[all] We're really sorry.
我们真的很抱歉。
[blender whirring]
（搅拌机嗡嗡声）
[all] Sorry!
抱歉！
Hmm.
嗯。
Perfect.
完美。
[blender whirring]
[搅拌机嗡嗡声]
That does not taste like forgiveness!
这味道可不像原谅啊！
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
- ♪ Na na na na na-na ♪ - ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
- ♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪ - ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
♪ Oh, hey, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ 哦，嘿，哦，哦，哦 ♪
- Anybody sleep last night?
- 昨晚有人睡觉了吗？
I tried to with my eyes open,
我试着睁着眼睛睡，
but it turns out that's just being awake.
但结果那只是醒着。
As long as we stick together, we have nothing to fear.
只要我们团结一致，就无所畏惧。
[dog barks]
[狗叫声]
[all] Hiyah!
[所有人] 嗨呀！
[whispers] Okay, Lou, we're all set for this weekend.
[低声] 好的，Lou，我们这周末都准备好了。
Uh-huh.
嗯哼。
It's a big surprise for my family.
这是我给家人准备的一个大惊喜。
Great, great. I'm very excited.
太好了，太好了。我非常兴奋。
- Hi, honey. - What surprise?
- 嗨，亲爱的。 - 什么惊喜？
Are you planning some sort of surprise?
你是不是在计划什么惊喜？
[laughs] No.
[笑] 没有。
Why, you want to hear it? 'Cause I have got to tell somebody.
为什么，你想听吗？因为我得告诉某个人。
No, as long as I have known you,
不，自从我认识你以来，
you have never been able to pull off a surprise.
你从来就没成功过搞个惊喜。
But I just love sharing!
但我就是喜欢分享！
I know, but then you share, you ruin the surprise,
我知道，但你一分享，惊喜就没了，
you get mad at yourself, and then nobody enjoys the thing
你又生自己的气，结果谁也没享受到
that was supposed to be fun.
原本应该有趣的事情。
You know what? Thank you, Anne.
你知道吗？谢谢你，Anne。
- You're right. - See?
- 你说得对。 - 看吧？
- Keep me strong. - [grunts]
- 让我坚强。 - [咕哝]
- Get this. I actually-- - [gasps]
- 听我说。我实际上—— - [吸气]
Control yourself, man.
控制住自己，伙计。
Secret-Strong, got it?
秘密-强，明白吗？
Guys, I think we're just being paranoid.
伙计们，我觉得我们只是有点多疑了。
I mean, Dawn might be mad,
我是说，Dawn可能会生气，
but she's not gonna sneak-attack us.
但她不会偷偷袭击我们的。
[all] Hiyah!
[所有人] 嗨呀！
Hiyah. [chuckles]
嗨呀。[轻笑]
Get this. On Saturday at the store--
听我说，周六在店里——
[Anne] Secret-Strong!
[Anne] 秘密-强！
Nicky's right about Dawn.
Nicky说得对，关于Dawn。
Let's just try to relax.
我们还是尽量放松吧。
[doorbell chimes]
[门铃响]
[all] Hiyah!
[所有人] 嗨呀！
We can't live like this.
我们不能这样生活。
We got to fix things with Dawn.
我们必须和Dawn解决问题。
One of us should probably answer the door first.
我们中应该有人先去开门。
[squeak]
[吱吱声]
[all] Hiyah!
[所有人] 嗨呀！
Stop it.
别这样。
- Sorry.
- 对不起。
[all sigh]
[所有人叹气]
[all whimper]
[所有人呜咽]
[all exhale]
[所有人叹气]
- Hey, guys.
- 嘿，伙计们。
[all] Hey, Mae.
[所有人] 嘿，梅。
I'm not allowed to talk to you, so if Dawn asks,
我不被允许和你说话，所以如果Dawn问起来，
that "Hey, guys" was really a "Hey, guys!"
那个“嘿，伙计们”其实是“嘿，伙计们！”
[squeak]
[吱吱声]
[all] Hiyah!
[所有人] 嗨呀！
And I'm gonna keep doing that
我会一直这样做
until they don't have any more tears left in their eye holes!
直到他们眼窝里再也没有泪水为止！
That's six empty eye holes.
那是六个空洞的眼窝。
[knocking on door]
（敲门声）
Knock, knock.
敲，敲。
Who's there?
谁啊？
It's not a knock-knock joke.
这不是一个敲门笑话。
It's not a knock-knock joke who?
这不是一个敲门笑话谁？
[sighs]
（叹气）
We're just gonna come in.
我们只是要进来。
Mae, since I am no longer speaking to these life-ruiners,
Mae，既然我不再和这些生活破坏者说话，
perhaps you should describe what I have planned for them.
也许你应该描述一下我为他们准备了什么计划。
No problem.
没问题。
You're not safe here.
你在这里不安全。
Just hear us out.
先听我们说完。
We thought, if you destroy some of our favorite things...
我们想，如果你毁掉我们一些心爱的东西……
And release some of your terrifying anger...
再发泄一些你那可怕的怒气……
It might make us even.
或许这样我们就能扯平了。
My space shuttle model.
我的太空梭模型。
This will be its last mission.
这将是它的最后一次任务。
My lucky wooden spoon.
我的幸运木勺。
It's whipped up some of my best dishes.
它曾搅拌过我的一些最佳菜肴。
And my most precious possession: my hair.
还有我最珍贵的宝贝：我的头发。
You may take one inch, no more.
你可以剪一英寸，不能再多了。
Tell them I'm so mad,
告诉他们我气得
I won't even touch their belongings.
连他们的东西都不会碰。
But Mae will.
但Mae会。
I will?
我会吗？
Start with the hair.
从头发开始。
Sorry.
对不起。
[snip]
咔嚓
[gasps] My baby!
哎呀！我的宝贝！
So everybody feels better, right?
这样大家都会感觉好些，对吧？
Now the spoon.
现在用勺子。
Forgive me.
请原谅我。
Woody!
伍迪！
Okay, so that should about do it.
好了，这样应该差不多了。
- Now the shuttle. - But, Dawn--
现在用穿梭机。
The shuttle!
穿梭机！
Tear ducts, we have a problem.
泪腺，我们有麻烦了。
[exhales]
呼气声
Okay.
好的。
Ask her if we're good.
问问她我们还好吗。
Are we good?
我们还好吗？
No, we're not good.
不，我们不好。
You can replace all those things,
那些东西你都可以换掉，
but you ruined my only chance to meet Candace Parker,
但你毁了我唯一一次见坎迪斯·帕克的机会，
and I'll never get that back.
我永远也找不回那个机会了。
[whispers] Sorry.
（低语）对不起。
[Dawn] Don't apologize, Mae!
（Dawn）Mae，别道歉！
[door closes]
（门关闭）
Well, that didn't go as planned.
嗯，事情没按计划进行。
We have to figure out a way for her to meet Candace Parker.
我们必须想办法让她见到坎迪斯·帕克。
It's the only way she'll forgive us.
这是她原谅我们的唯一办法。
Good idea.
好主意。
I'll find out where she's staying.
我会查出她住在哪里。
And I'll work a little Dicky magic
然后我会施展一点迪基的魔法
and get us an appointment.
帮我们预约见面。
Knock, knock.
敲敲门。
Who's there?
谁啊？
Dawn wants you out of her room.
道恩让你离开她的房间。
Dawn wants you out of her room who?
道恩让你离开她的房间，谁啊？
[Dawn] Get out!
出去！
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
哦，哦，哦
We're really glad you gave us a chance to make things right.
我们真的很高兴你给了我们一个机会来弥补
So I'm really going to meet Candace?
所以我真的要见Candace？
Yes.
是的
- Candace Parker? - Yes.
- Candace Parker？ - 是的
Candace Parker the basketball player,
篮球运动员Candace Parker，
not some other random person
不是某个也叫Candace Parker的随机其他人？
whose name also happens to be Candace Parker?
会有其他叫Candace Parker的随机人
Would some random person named Candace Parker
开着这个到处跑吗？
ride around in this?
开着这个到处跑？
That's a dumpster.
那是个垃圾箱。
Oh. Sorry. Wrong arm.
哦，抱歉，搞错手臂了。
[gasps]
（倒吸气）
The Candace Cruiser?
凯蒂斯巡洋舰？
Yep, Nicky and I tracked it down,
是的，我和尼基找到了它，
and Dicky made an appointment with Candace.
迪基和凯蒂丝预约了见面。
I did?
我约了吗？
Why did you say "I did?" instead of "I did"?
你为什么说“我约了吗？”而不是直接说“我约了”？
Well, I did make an appointment
嗯，我的确预约了
to fix my hair.
来修我的头发。
So you did nothing?
所以你什么都没做？
Are you not listening?
你没在听吗？
Look at me.
看着我。
I'm back to perfect.
我又完美了。
So Candace doesn't even know we're here?
所以Candace甚至不知道我们在这里？
[scoffs] Wow.
[嗤笑] 哇。
Why do you guys hate me?
你们为什么都讨厌我？
Oh, it's because I'm taller, isn't it?
哦，是因为我更高，对吧？
Dawn, we don't hate you.
Dawn，我们并不讨厌你。
Look, we're here.
看，我们在这儿。
Let me just smooth talk us in.
让我来用甜言蜜语把我们带进去。
Yo, Candace!
哟，Candace！
I don't think she's in here.
我觉得她不在这里。
But all her stuff is.
但她的东西都在。
You should really see this, Dawn.
你真的应该看看这个，Dawn。
You know, you guys don't respect anyone's privacy.
你们知道吗，你们不尊重任何人的隐私。
First mine, now hers.
先是我的，现在又是她的。
You know, we shouldn't even be in here--
你们知道，我们甚至不应该进来的——
Oh, is that her jersey?
哦，那是她的球衣吗？
[camera shutter clicking]
[相机快门声]
Okay, I've taken a picture with everything in here.
好了，我已经和这里的一切都拍了照。
Now we can leave.
现在我们可以离开了。
Hold on.
等等。
I think you're forgetting something.
我觉得你忘了什么。
What?
什么？
Eh...
呃...
maybe a thank-you?
也许是一声谢谢？
For what?
为了什么？
You know, eh...
你知道，呃...
I still didn't meet Candace.
我还没见到Candace。
Eh...
呃...
but you met her stuff.
但你见到了她的东西。
Eh...
呃...
nice try.
不错的尝试。
Now let's go before somebody comes.
现在我们走吧，免得有人来。
[all scream]
[大家都尖叫]
Sorry I'm late, guys.
抱歉我迟到了，伙计们。
I'll be your driver,
我将担任你们的司机，
J.D. McCoy.
J.D. McCoy。
Ah, that's right.
啊，没错。
I heard you don't speak, uh, very good English,
我听说你的英语，呃，不是很好，
and I don't speak a lick of Russian,
而我一句俄语也不会说，
but in any language,
但无论什么语言，
make yourselves at home!
请随意，就像在自己家一样！
Russian?
俄语？
[Russian accent] Uh, in any language, we go now.
（俄国口音）呃，无论什么语言，我们现在出发。
Ah, yes.
啊，是的。
We go now.
我们现在出发。
And don't worry, I'll get you there safely
别担心，我会安全地把你们送到目的地
with the smoothest stops and starts you've ever felt,
以你从未体验过的最平稳的启停，
or my name isn't
否则我的名字就不叫
J.D. McCoy.
J.D. 麦考伊。
Oh, no!
哦，不！
Where's the bus going?
公交车要去哪里？
[speaking Russian]
[说俄语]
[all] No!
[所有人]不！
[all] Nyet!
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ 哦，哦 ♪
- Ooh, this is not good.
哦，这不太妙。
- Where do you think J.D. McCoy's taking us?
- 你觉得J.D. McCoy要把我们带到哪儿去？
I have no idea.
我不知道。
Well, he thinks we're Russian, so he must be driving to Russia.
嗯，他认为我们是俄罗斯人，所以他一定是在开车去俄罗斯。
You can't drive to Russia, Dicky.
你不能开车去俄罗斯，Dicky。
I can't, but if anybody can, it's J.D. McCoy.
我不能，但如果有人能做到，那就是J.D. McCoy。
Maybe we should look for clues
也许我们应该找找线索
to find out who J.D. McCoy thinks we are.
来弄清楚J.D. McCoy认为我们是谁。
[all scream]
[大家尖叫]
[Russian accent] Who is driving bus?
[俄语口音]谁在开巴士？
Um, nobody.
呃，没人。
I just pulled over.
我刚靠边停车。
About a mile back,
大约一英里前，
I realized that something is not right with you.
我就意识到你有些不对劲。
- Uh-oh.
哎呀。
You guys are not
你们没有
in costume. - Costume?
穿戏服。 - 戏服？
Oh, that's right.
哦，对了。
You no speak-y Engl-y.
你不会说英语。
You in here.
你在这里。
Arm-ski, arm-ski, leg-ski, leg-ski,
手臂，手臂，腿，腿，
zip-ski up-ski.
拉链-斯基，向上-斯基。
It's almost showtime.
演出快开始了。
[Russian accent] Yeah, yeah, showtime.
[俄罗斯口音] 是，是，演出时间。
What's showtime?
什么是演出时间？
You know what, we could've been off this bus,
你知道吗，我们本可以离开这辆巴士的，
but no.
但是没有。
You had to have a thank-you, so you know what?
你非要来个感谢，所以你知道吗？
Here you go!
给你！
Thank you!
谢谢！
You're welcome!
不客气！
I guess we should just put these on
我想我们应该先戴上这些
until we come up with a plan.
直到我们想出一个计划。
[phone ringing]
[电话铃声]
Oh, no, it's Mom and Dad.
哦，不，是爸爸妈妈。
- Don't answer. - Well, I have to.
- 别接。 - 我得接。
Otherwise, they'll think something's up.
否则他们会觉得有什么事。
Something is up.
确实有事。
But they can't know that.
但他们不能知道。
We told them we were going to Mae's house.
我们告诉他们我们要去梅家。
[sighs]
[叹气]
Hey, Dad.
We're just at Mae's doing stuff with Mae
at Mae's.
Okay, well, we need you to meet us at Get Sporty!
for the biggest surprise of your life!
- They're all the same! - No, they're not.
Shh!
Oh, honey, you must have pressed video chat.
I'm staring straight into your ear.
Can you pull the phone back a bit?
[whispers] She's gonna see we're on a bus.
[低语] 她会看到我们在公交车上。
Did you just say you're on a bus?
你刚才是说你在公交车上吗？
Uh, no, I said, "Mae's house is full of dust."
呃，不，我说的是，“梅的家满是灰尘。”
Why are you holding the phone so close to your face?
你为什么把手机拿得离脸这么近？
Uh, Mae's mom doesn't want you to see her dusty, dusty house.
呃，梅的妈妈不想让你看到她那满是灰尘的房子。
Uh...
呃...
[high-pitched voice] That's true, Anne.
[高音调] 那是真的，安妮。
You know how I like to keep a clean house.
你知道我喜欢保持房子干净。
Uh...
呃...
[deep voice] That's news to me, Evelyn.
[低沉声音] 这对我来说是新闻，伊芙琳。
It's nothing like my mother's house, I'll tell you that.
我告诉你，那跟我妈家完全不一样。
Oh, you like it there so much?
哦，你那么喜欢那里吗？
Why don't you go back there?
那你为什么不回去呢？
At least there I get three hot meals.
至少在那里我还能吃到三顿热饭。
Um, got to go. See you at the store.
嗯，我得走了。在店里见。
What the heck was that?
那到底是怎么回事？
Sounds like trouble in paradise.
听起来像是天堂里的麻烦。
We got to get off this bus.
我们得下车了。
Hey, I think we're slowing down.
嘿，我觉得我们正在减速。
As soon as the bus stops,
一旦公交车停下，
we bolt out of those doors and go to the store.
我们立刻冲出车门，去那家店。
[brakes hiss]
[刹车声]
Go, go, go!
快，快，快！
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
哇，哇，哇。
[boys] Candace Parker?
Candace Parker？
Whoa, you said my name with no Russian accent.
哇，你叫我的名字居然没有俄罗斯口音。
[Russian accent] Oh, they mean Candace Parker?
哦，他们说的是Candace Parker？
Sorry I'm late.
抱歉我迟到了。
I'm so thrilled to finally be meeting From Russia with Funk.
我太激动了，终于能见到《From Russia with Funk》了。
I love seeing you guys bring it whenever I play in Russia.
我喜欢在俄罗斯比赛时看到你们带来的活力。
[Russian accent] Um, bring what exactly?
[俄罗斯口音] 嗯，具体带什么来呢？
The funk, when you dance.
带节奏，你们跳舞的时候。
- [Russian accent] Of course. - [Russian accent] The funk.
- [俄罗斯口音] 当然。 - [俄罗斯口音] 带节奏。
[Russian accent] We bring it everywhere.
[俄罗斯口音] 我们到处都带。
Well, since we're going to be working together,
既然我们要一起工作，
I should probably get to know your names.
我应该了解一下你们的名字。
- Uh, Nickski. - Rickski.
- 呃，尼克斯基。 - 里克斯基。
Uh, Dickski.
呃，迪克斯基。
And Dawn...ski.
还有，道恩...斯基。
Well, since we're almost there, I should get changed.
既然我们快到了，我应该换一下衣服。
This is gonna be the best workout video ever.
这将是史上最棒的健身视频。
[Russian accent] Nice to meet me, Candace Parker!
很高兴见到我，我是坎迪斯·帕克！
[normal voice] Wait, wait, wait, workout video?
等等，等等，健身视频？
With funk?
还有放克音乐？
We got to get off this bus.
我们得下车。
Too late.
太迟了。
We're moving.
车已经开动了。
Wow, J.D. McCoy's starts are smoother than his stops.
哇，J.D.麦考伊的起步比他的停车要顺畅多了。
[whistling melody]
（吹口哨旋律）
We're here, Anne.
我们到了，安妮。
Oh, you are doing great, honey.
哦，你做得很好，亲爱的。
You haven't ruined the surprise yet.
你还没有破坏惊喜。
Stay Secret-Strong.
保持秘密强大。
[both laugh]
（两人笑）
Okay, here, wait. Take my arm.
好的，这里，等等。扶着我的手臂。
Okay. [clears throat]
好的。（清嗓子）
Whoa. [laughs] Whoa.
哇。（笑）哇。
Tom, when I'm blindfolded,
汤姆，当我蒙着眼睛时，
it feels like you actually have muscles!
感觉你真的有肌肉！
[gasps]
（喘气）
That's Lou's arm.
那是Lou的手臂。
Who's Lou?
Lou是谁？
He's the guy I'm working with
他就是我和我一起工作的那个人。
and the man whose biceps you're fondling.
也是你正在抚摸其二头肌的那位。
You can stop now.
你现在可以停下来了。
Harper, it's almost go time.
Harper，差不多是时候开始了。
You promised me a flawless production,
你答应我会有一个完美的制作，
and you better deliver.
你最好能做到。
Or?
否则呢？
Else.
否则。
[sighs]
[叹气]
Oh, no.
哦，不。
Else is the worst.
否则是最糟糕的。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
Okay, listen, as soon as the bus stops,
好的，听着，一旦巴士停下，
we're going to make our move.
我们就要行动了。
[all scream]
[所有人尖叫]
[Russian accent] We are stopped?
[俄罗斯口音] 我们停下了吗？
Oh, yeah, I told you,
哦，是的，我告诉过你，
J.D. McCoy would get you here smooth-ski and safe-ski.
J.D. McCoy会让你顺利且安全地到达。
[Russian accent] Yes, but where-ski exact-ski?
是的，但具体在哪里？
[slowly] Colorado.
科罗拉多。
Go, go, go.
走，走，走。
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
哇，哇，哇。
You guys are in a hurry to get started, huh?
你们这么急着开始，是吗？
We're shooting the video at a place called Tom's Get Sporty!
我们将在一个叫汤姆的体育馆拍摄视频！
You guys ever heard of it?
你们听说过吗？
Yeah, me neither.
是啊，我也没听说过。
Anyways, I'll see you guys in there.
总之，我们里面见。
♪
Oh, I wish I could wait for the kids, but here comes the surprise, Anne.
哦，我真希望能等孩子们，但惊喜来了，安妮。
- Take them off. Take them off. - Okay.
脱掉，脱掉。
- Is that Candace Parker? - Yep.
好的。
I convinced the director, Lou, to shoot her workout video
那是坎迪斯·帕克吗？
here in the store.
是的。
Okay, not only am I proud of you
我说服了导演卢，在这里的店里拍摄她的健身视频。
for finally pulling off a surprise,
好吧，我不仅为你终于成功制造了一个惊喜而感到骄傲，
but this one is really good.
而且这个惊喜真的很棒。
Dawn is gonna freak out!
道恩会疯掉的！
I am freaking out.
我已经在疯掉了。
They're shooting Candace's video at Dad's store!
他们在爸爸的店里拍摄Candace的视频！
How funny is that?
这有多搞笑？
You would've met Candace anyway.
反正你本来就会遇到Candace。
What a crazy little world.
这世界真是小得疯狂。
This must be Dad's big surprise.
这一定是爸爸的大惊喜。
The bigger surprise is when he finds out
更大的惊喜是他发现
From Russia with Funk is not from Russia
《来自俄罗斯的Funk》不是来自俄罗斯
and does not have any funk
也没有任何Funk元素
and is us.
而是我们。
Well, don't worry. I got funk.
嗯，别担心。我有Funk。
You got funk like the real From Russia with Funk?
你真的有那种《俄罗斯之韵》里的那种funk吗？
[hip-hop music]
[嘻哈音乐]
♪ ♪
Dicky don't got funk like that funk.
迪基可没有那种funk。
[sighs]
[叹气]
We can't ruin this video for Mom, Dad, and Candace.
我们不能毁了爸妈和坎迪斯看的这个视频。
We just have to come clean and tell them what happened.
我们只能坦白告诉他们发生了什么。
Dad always appreciates our honesty.
爸爸总是欣赏我们的诚实。
And that's how we ended up on her bus.
就这样，我们上了她的车。
- Okay. - Thank you.
好的。谢谢。
You know I always appreciate your honesty.
你知道我总是欣赏你的诚实。
[Lou] Harper!
哈珀！
Now get out there and dance.
现在出去跳舞吧。
But, Dad, we're not Russian dancers.
但是，爸爸，我们不是俄罗斯舞者。
You want to tell him that?
你想告诉他吗？
What is this?
这是什么？
Chocolate sprinkles?
巧克力糖粒？
I asked for rainbow jimmies.
我要的是彩虹糖针。
You're fired.
你被解雇了。
[all] Mom?
妈妈？
Sorry, kids, but you see Lou.
对不起，孩子们，但你们看Lou。
He's just so big and...
他只是那么大而且...
muscular and--
肌肉发达而且--
We get it, Anne.
我们明白了，安妮。
Hi, I'm Candace Parker.
嗨，我是坎迪斯·帕克。
Welcome to my workout,
欢迎来到我的锻炼课程，
where I combine basketball, exercise, and hip-hop,
我将篮球、锻炼和嘻哈结合在一起，
or as I like to call it, Hip-Hoop.
或者我称之为嘻哈篮球。
No matter what language you speak,
无论你说什么语言，
good health translates to good life,
良好的健康意味着良好的生活，
so here to help me is my favorite dance crew,
所以在这里帮助我的是我最喜欢的舞蹈团队，
From Russia with Funk.
来自俄罗斯的Funk舞团。
So let's start off with some basic moves.
那么让我们从一些基本动作开始。
Cut!
停！
Oh, he is so loud.
哦，他声音真大。
What the heck was that?
那到底是什么鬼？
You know what, lose the basketballs.
你知道吗，把篮球放下。
Do what you guys do best.
做你们最擅长的事。
I hope your hip is better than your hoop.
我希望你的hip比你的hoop强。
[hip-hop music]
[嘻哈音乐]
Dance already!
快跳舞吧！
Ah, please dance!
啊，请跳舞！
♪ ♪
Cut!
停！
Did you leave your funk in Russia?
你的节奏感留在俄罗斯了吗？
Nope, they left it on the side of the road.
没有，他们把它丢在路边了。
Who are you?
你是谁？
[all] He's J.D. McCoy.
[所有人] 他是J.D. McCoy。
And J.D. McCoy always delivers his passengers
而J.D. McCoy总是能平稳安全地送达他的乘客。
smoothly and safely.
这些孩子才是真正的‘从俄罗斯带来的节奏’。
These kids are the real From Russia with Funk.
这些孩子才是真正的'俄罗斯来的放克'。
Who are they?
他们是谁？
They're from Boulder and have no funk at all.
他们来自博尔德，根本不懂放克。
Well, no matter who they are,
好吧，不管他们是谁，
I got them here smoothly and safely.
我已经顺利安全地把他们送到了这里。
And now I'll be on my way.
现在我要继续我的旅程。
Destination unknown.
目的地未知。
Actually, I'm just gonna go wait in the bus.
实际上，我打算去巴士里等着。
Well, uh, why don't we pick it up from the top?
那么，我们为什么不从头再来一遍？
I don't know what you and your kids are up to,
我不知道你和你的孩子们在搞什么，
but congratulations, you're ruining Candace's video.
但恭喜了，你们正在毁掉坎迪斯的视频。
[sighs] Dang it.
哎呀，糟糕。
That's the last thing I wanted to do.
这正是我最不想做的事。
I'm really, really sorry, Candace.
我真的，真的很抱歉，坎迪斯。
Dawn, you don't have to apologize.
道恩，你不必道歉。
It was our fault.
这是我们的错。
We ruined our sister's chance of having lunch with you.
我们毁了姐姐和你共进午餐的机会。
And she really deserved to win.
而且她真的应该赢。
She knows more about you than anybody.
她比你任何人都更了解你。
Well, then she knows I have brothers,
那么她就知道我有兄弟，
and they ruined a lot of things for me growing up.
他们在我成长过程中毁了很多东西。
See? She gets us.
看吧？她懂我们。
Okay, now that the real dancers are here,
好了，既然真正的舞者来了，
are we doing this shoot or not?
我们是要拍这个还是不拍？
Pipe down, Lou.
安静点，Lou。
Brothers, am I right?
兄弟们，对吧？
Wait, he's your brother?
等等，他是你兄弟？
Little brother.
小弟。
[laughs]
[笑]
[coughs]
[咳嗽]
[mouths words]
[嘴型示意]
And he's always butting in.
他总是插手。
You know what that's like, Dawn.
你知道那种感觉，Dawn。
Tell me about it.
说得太对了。
What do you say we take five and go shoot some hoops?
我们休息五分钟，去投篮怎么样？
But, Candace, what about the video shoot?
但是，Candace，视频拍摄怎么办？
I'm telling Mom.
我要告诉妈妈。
Have you ever dunked?
你扣过篮吗？
Only cookies in milk.
只在牛奶里泡过饼干。
Well, that was a win-win.
那倒是双赢。
Dawn got to meet her hero,
Dawn见到了她的偶像，
and I actually pulled off a surprise.
而我真的成功制造了一个惊喜。
[laughs] You stayed Secret-Strong.
[笑]你保持了秘密的力量。
Yeah, I'm gonna do the same thing for your big birthday surprise.
是的，我也会为你生日的大惊喜做同样的事。
- Get this. - Ooh.
- 看这个。 - 哦。
- I got front-row seats-- - Oh.
- 我拿到了前排座位-- - 哦。
This is way better than cookies and milk.
这比饼干和牛奶好多了。
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
[whistling]
[口哨声]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪